# **NATHAN WILKINS**

Austin, TX 479-409-0876 nathanwilkins01@gmail.com

MERN-Stack Developer with a specialty in utilizing front-end design to communicate clients' missions. With a decade of managing, directing, and booking a full-staff music venue & world-touring band under my belt, I have learned to adapt with my constantly changing environment and meet every task with optimism and excitement.

I take pride in creating meaningful user experiences, bridging the gap between user and client. At the core of my work is a passion for community and the spirit of collaboration, something that makes me a reliable teammate in any scenario.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Talent Buyer | Event Coordinator**

07/2016 to Present

Quack's Bakery, LLC

Austin, TX

- Oversees all event booking
- · Negotiates guarantees for performers
- · Coordinates Staff Schedule based on show needs
- Hires marketing artists
- · Communicates between artists and staff for proper timing
- Handles payout at end of the night

## **Managing Director | Lead Performer**

10/2011 to Present

Hikes Music, LLC

Austin, TX

- Oversees all internal operations
- · Coordinates team schedule
- · Main point of contact for all business affairs
- · Oversees all finances
- Manages Payroll
- Lead Songwriter
- Manages social media

#### **Music Educator**

07/2015 to Present

Mother Falcon Music Lab

Austin, TX

- · Creates new curriculum yearly
- · Organizes lessons based on students needs
- Helps facilitate ~100 students weekly
- · Coordinates with co-workers to improve the overall communication and effectiveness of daily lessons
- Adapts to students needs and concerns

# Social Media Manager | Content Creator

01/2017 to 01/2019

The House Of Songs

Bentonville, AR | Austin, TX

- · Oversees all social media content on 4 platforms
- · Communicates with Manager and monthly Artists in residence
- · Schedules content creation sessions with Artists
- Travels to accommodate artists
- · Keeps a daily feed of new social media content across 4 platforms

#### **SKILLS**

Contract Negotiation - 9 years

Finance - 9 years

Bilingual - 3 years

Marketing Campaign Management - 5 years

JavaScript - 1 year

HTML - 1 year

User Interface Design - 1 year

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Farmington High School**

High school or equivalent Music Composition Fayetteville, AR 08/2006 to 06/2010

#### **CERTIFICATIONS / LICENSES**

# **University of Texas Full-Stack Development Certificate**

06/2020 to 01/2021

Full Stack Development course through the University of Texas.